https://www.manierherod.com/privacy-policy/

from
users of this website. In this policy, you can learn what kind of
information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how
we
protect the information, and the choices you have with respect to
your personal
information.
What personal information is collected through this website
and how is it used?
We collect information
about our users in three ways: directly
from
the user, from our Web server logs and through cookies. We use the
information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet
Policy, or when we believe in good
faith that the law requires it.
User-supplied information: If you fill out the
“contact” form on this website, we will ask you to provide some personal
information (such as e-mail address, name, phone number and state).
We
only require that you provide an e-mail address on the contact form.
Further, if chat is available through this site, you may be asked to
provide information if you participate in an online chat. Please do not
submit any confidential, proprietary or sensitive personally
identifiable information (e.g. Social Security Number; date of birth;
drivers license number; or credit card, bank account or other financial
information) (collectively, “Sensitive Information”). If you submit any
Sensitive Information, you do so at your own risk and we will not be
liable to you or responsible for consequences of your submission.
Information that you provide to us through the contact form or an
online chat will be used so that we may respond to your inquiry. We may
also use information you provide to us to communicate with you in the
future. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may opt
out (unsubscribe) as described below.
Web server logs: When you visit our website, we may
track information about your visit and store that information in web
server logs, which are records of the activities on our sites. The
servers automatically capture and save the information electronically.
Examples of the information we may collect include:
your unique Internet protocol address; the name of your unique Internet service provider; the town/city, county/state and country from which you access our website; the kind of browser or computer you use; the number of links you click within the site; the date and time of your visit; the web page from which you arrived to our site; the pages you viewed on the site; and certain searches/queries that you conducted via our website(s).
The
information we collect in web server logs helps us administer
the site, analyze
its usage, protect the website and its content from
inappropriate use and
improve the user’s experience.
Cookies: In order to offer and provide a customized
and personal service, our websites and applications may use cookies and
similar technologies to store and help track information about you.
Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser
from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use
cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate our sites
during your visits. Cookies also can tell us where visitors go on a
website and allow us to save preferences for you so you won’t have to
re-enter them each time you visit. The use of cookies is relatively
standard. Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies,
but you can use your browser to either notify you when you receive a
cookie or to disable cookies.
If you wish to disable cookies from this site, you can do so using your
browser.
You should understand that some features of many sites may
not function properly if you don’t accept cookies.
For more information
about using browsers to manage cookies, please see All About Cookies.
You can also refuse to accept Flash cookies from this website using Adobe’s Flash management tools. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ad Settings.
By visiting this website, you consent to the use of cookies and similar technologies in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
Third-party Services: We may use services hosted by
third parties, including Adobe Site Catalyst, to assist in providing our
services and to help us understand the use of our site by our visitors.
These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a
web page request, including your IP address or cookies. If these
third-party services collect information, they do so anonymously and in
the aggregate to provide information helpful to us such as website
trends, without identifying individual visitors.
In addition, we may use services provided by third parties to display
relevant content, products, services and advertising to you. These third
parties may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to
collect or receive information from this website and elsewhere on the
internet. They may then use that information to provide measurement
services so we can understand your interests and retarget advertisements
based on your previous visits to this website. Please keep in mind that
we do not share your personal information with any third-party
advertiser, ad server or ad network.
You may be able to opt-out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting by some third parties by visiting www.aboutads.info/choices.
You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ad Settings. You can visit this page
to opt out of AdRoll’s and their partners’ targeted advertising. Please
see “Cookies” in the section above for more information on how you can
control the use of cookies on your computer.
California Do Not Track: Our web services do not
alter, change, or respond upon receiving Do Not Track (DNT) requests or
signals in browsers.
As described in more detail above, we track user
activity using web server logs, cookies and similar technologies.
Information collected in web server logs helps us analyze website usage
and improve the user’s experience. Cookies allow us to offer you a
customized experience and present relevant advertising to you.
How is personal information protected?
We take certain appropriate
security measures to help protect your
personal information from accidental
loss and from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. However, we cannot
guarantee that unauthorized
persons will always be unable to defeat our security
measures.
Who has access to the information?
We
will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other user data to
others, and
we will not make your personal information available to
any unaffiliated
parties, except as follows:
to agents, website vendors and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us; if we are unable to assist with your matter, but know an
unaffiliated attorney or firm that may be able to help you, we may refer
you and share information you provided us with that party; and as required by law, in a matter of public safety
or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business
assets (for example, if we are acquired by another firm or if we are
liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good
faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or
property.
How can I correct, amend or
delete my personal information and/or opt out of future communications?
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any
time. Contact
us via the phone number,
contact form or mailing address on our website
at any time to:
see what data we have about you, if any;change/correct any data we have about you;ask us to delete any data we have about you; and/oropt out of future communications from us.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this privacy
policy, please contact us via the phone number, contact form or mailing
address listed on this website. If our information practices change in a
significant way, we will post the policy changes here.
Effective September 14, 2015
Practice Areas
Bankruptcy and Creditors' RightsCivil LitigationCommercial and Professional Liability Insurance CoverageConstruction LawEmployment LawEntertainment, Sports, and Intellectual Property LitigationEstate Planning and ProbateFidelity Law and Cyber Insurance CoverageReal EstateSurety LawTax and Business Succession PlanningTax, Business and CommercialWorkers' Compensation
